<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="tap_jacking_alert">Your screen is being obscured by another app. Please close any overlays and try again.</string>
    <string name="rooted_critical">Rooted devices/emulators are not supported for this application.</string>
    <string name="rooted_warning">Rooted devices or emulators can pose significant security risks.</string>
    <string name="vpn_warning">Active VPN connection detected, which may pose potential security risks.</string>
    <string name="proxy_warning">Active Proxy connection detected, which may pose potential security risks.</string>
    <string name="unsecured_network_warning">An unsecured network connection has been detected.</string>
    <string name="auto_time_warning">As per regulation, date &amp; time cannot be set manually. Please change date-time setting to automatic mode &amp; try again.</string>
    <string name="developer_options_warning">As per regulation, &quot;Developer Options&quot; must not be enabled. Please disable &quot;Developer Options&quot; &amp; try again.</string>
    <string name="mock_location_warning">Mock location is enabled, which may affect the accuracy of location data.</string>
    <string name="usb_debugging_warning">USB debugging is enabled, which may pose security risks.</string>
    <string name="app_spoofing_warning">Application spoofing has been detected, which may compromise security.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_warning">Accessibility Service is enabled for this app.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_not_warning">Accessibility Service is not enabled for this app.</string>
    <string name="screen_sharing_warning">Screen sharing is active, which may pose a security risk.</string>
    <string name="screen_mirroring_warning">Screen mirroring is active, which may pose a security risk.</string>
    <string name="screen_recording_warning">Screen recording is active, which may pose a security risk.</string>
    <string name="app_signature_warning">App verification failed! The app signature does not match the expected credentials. This may indicate unauthorized changes or tampering.</string>
    <string name="app_signature_critical">App signature invalid! Potential tampering or unauthorized modification detected. The app cannot proceed and will now terminate.</string>
    <string name="in_call_warning">Please note an active call is detected. This might be a security risk.</string>
    <string name="in_call_critical">Please note an active call is detected. This might be a security risk.</string>
    <string name="ongoing_call_warning">Please note an active call is detected. This might be a security risk.</string>
    <string name="ongoing_call_critical">Please note an active call is detected. This might be a security risk.</string>

</resources>
